PAUL NARVAS

MSc, BSc (Hons), ACIAT
ARCHITECTURAL TECHNOLOGIST

Introduction

An Architectural Technologist and has valuable experience working for both consultancies and contractors where I've been responsible for co-ordinating teams on projects.

With experience working in the mixed -used sectors, residential, commercial, hotel and offices and renovation, listed building and Modular.

Experience working onsite and gaining a thorough understanding of site considerations, requirements, and potential issues.

I have comprehensive experience of working with AutoCAD, Sketchup and Revit. Have an interest in innovative, functional design.

I believe teamwork and communication is a vital part of a successful outcome.

Education & Professional status

- BS(Hons) Architectural Technology, Sheffield Hallam University
- MSc Technical Architecture Sheffield Hallam University
- · ACIAT Architectural Technologist

Key Attributes

- Experienced Multi-Disciplinary Design
- · Concept Design & Detailed Design
- AutoCAD, Revit and Sketchup
- · Design Management

Contact

TEL: 07525496910

EMAIL: paul@narvas.co.uk
WEBSITE: paulnarvas.com

Additional Information:

Driving License: Full and clean

Scan this QR code on your camera app to go to my digital portfolio

PAULNARVAS.COM



Experience

JRL MODULAR LTD, NEWARK (2022-PRESENT)

Design Manager Responsible for coordinating/running projects with contractors and sub-contractors, Architects and design management and procurement.

DB3 ARCHITECTS, LEEDS (2020-2022)

Lossiemouth MOD Accommodation, Scotland

Senior Architectural Technologist Working on delivering detailed design for the construction of a new modular for Lossiemouth MOD accommodation scheme for Caledonian Modular.

CCE Wakefield Walk on Ceiling, Wakefield

Working on walk on ceiling replacement for Coca Cola Wakefield. Providing Tender and construction drawings.

DIXON DAWSON CHARTERED ARCHITECTS, SHEFFIELD (2016-2020)

Senior Architectural Technologist at Dixon Dawson Chartered Architects, Sheffield. Working on a £50m retail, leisure, hotel, restaurant and office scheme for Waverley in Rotherham and Stroud redevelopment.

Waverley, Rotherham

Working on a new £50m, Retail, leisure and office scheme. The scheme received a permission in a record time with no objections. The new development by Waverley Square Limited, a joint venture between Harworth Group Plc and Dransfield Properties Ltd, is a central part in the ongoing regeneration of the 740-acre Waverley site, Yorkshire largest ever brownfield development. The genuinely outstanding scheme befitting of Waverly with architecture and materials to match so to serve this growing and thriving community. Responsibilities included providing concept design, Planning and Building Regulations, Tender and Construction drawings.

Marywalks Centre, Stroud, Gloucestershire

Working on redevelopment, reconfiguration of the external alterations to the existing mall, car park and cinema, including new entrance feature, access arrangement, extension and demolition works and internal alteration, conversion works to and change of use to incorporate new hotel and restaurant.

Market Street & North Street, Gainsborough

Working on major development of a key town centre site – Including a brand-new hotel. Plans were approved by West Lindsey District Council's. The first phase of work will deliver the new hotel and ponti's Italian restaurant on the ground floor including an attractive alfresco dining area and water feature inspired by Paley Park in New York. Responsibilities included preparing planning and Building Regulations drawings, tender and construction drawings. The idea is to transform a run down and tired area within a market town.

CORDONIER ARCHITECTS, SHEFFIELD (2007-2016)

Senior Architectural Technologist. Working on a project from £50,000 to £9M on construction management, design and build and traditional procurement. Duties have included preparing technical drawings and details for submission to building control and local planning authorities, mostly on various high-end residential projects, care homes and also some educational projects, both new build and conversions this involves close working partnerships with various consultants/engineers etc.

Ryecroft Glen, Dore, Sheffield

Senior Architectural Technologist Lead and main contact for Sheffield City Council and Consultant. Working on 10 new apartments with associated undercroft car parking accommodation. Responsible for planning and Building Regulations drawings and submission. Tender and construction drawings. Overseeing the design/construction progress and detailed design stages.

References: Available upon request.